Jarrel Thomas

(951) 232-0215 jarrel.thomas@gmail.com 2953 Marvin Circle, Maryville TN Forward-thinking IT professional with several years of experience in diagnostics and remediation of a wide variety of web technologies and websites. Utilizes highly attuned analytical skills to increase productivity and performance of web technologies and systems at scale.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (Computer Information System)

Florida Institute of Technology 2020

EXPERIENCE

Technical Support Engineer

Twilio · June 2021 - Present

- Utilize Splunk, Snowflake to analyze traffic, activity, and events across the environment.
- Create and maintain thorough internal documentation for issues, investigation methodologies, resolution summary
- Reading/Debugging HTML, XML, JavaScript, React, SQL
- Good knowledge of RESTful technology, working with APIs and ability to understand and solve issues with cloud solutions

Help Desk Technician

City of Redlands · July 2019 - June 2021

- Developed group policy scripts to automate system administrator tasks
- Configured and deployed a variety of computer images
- Installed computers, peripheral equipment, hardware upgrades, and software
- Continuously integrated and deployed developed software. Updated the continuous integration/deployment scripts as necessary to improve continuous integration practices
- Maintained, updated, and modified the school website
- Assisted in the testing and improvement of city data analytical software
- Resolved technical issues through remote desktop
- Documented all help desk work orders through a ticketing system

Help Desk Technician (Level 2)

Santa Rosa Academy · October 2018 - July 2019

- Configured and distributed new Macbooks & Chromebooks
- · Configured and deployed computer images
- Installed computers, peripheral equipment, hardware upgrades, and software
- Assisted with managing Google domain and administration of those Chromebooks
- Assisted in monitoring network traffic through OpenDNS
- · Maintained, updated and modified school website
- Assisted with the management of the tech department inventory of equipment and licenses.
- Assisted in managing email campaigns to staff and parents about school events
- Resolved technical issues through remote desktop